Guide to the Heinz Eulau Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2004-55
  - Eckstein, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - MiMa: Unit Level and Comparison, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Book Outlines, Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Bibliography, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - David Yoffic Memos, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - The Career Data, Memos, Etc., 1969-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - John Manley, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Political Science Stanford University, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Report to Dean on Stanford Dept., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Chronical File Sept. 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Political Science Instruction at Stanford, 1973 May (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Stanford Memos, 1973 & 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Congress LSQ, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Departemental Memoranda, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gilliam Case, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Rotteroam Contexts, 1966-1985 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Letters of Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Inter-university Consortium for Political and Social Research Documents and Publications, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 13-25)
  - Kuklinski Project, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 41643)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "G", 1964-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "H", 1963-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "I", 1974-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "J", 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "K", 1979-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "L", 1969-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "M", 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "N", 1972-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "O", 1977-1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "P", 1974-1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "Q", 1963-1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "R", 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "S", 1975-1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "T", 1966-1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "U-V", 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "W", 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Letters of Correspondence People with last name "X-Z", 1973-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - New Reports, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Lectures/Papers 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Walter Lippmann: The Eisenhower Years, 1963 June (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Context American PS, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Letters of Correspondence, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 41641)
  - Letters of Correspondence, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Matthew's Conference Seattle Materials, Notes, etc., 1995 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - American Political Science Assoication Boston, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Archival Idea, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1961-1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Governmetnal Studies University of California, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Del Sesto: "Nuclear Reactor Safety and the Role of the Congressman Content Analysis of Congression", 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Jernberg: "Information Change and Congressional Behavior: A Caveat for PPB Reformers", 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Buckwalter: "The Cong. Concurrent Resolution: A search for Foreign Policy Influence", 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Fox: "Congress and U.S. Military Service in the Post-War Period: A Research Note", 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Westefield. "Majority Part Leadrship and the Committee System in the House of Representatives", 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dyson and Soule: "Cong. Comm. Behavior on Roll Cali Votes: The U.S. House of Representatives, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Entin: "Information Exchange in Congress: The Case of the House Armed Service Committee", 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Jahnige, "The Congressional Committee System and the Oversight Princess: Congress and NASA", 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Introduction Background, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mover+Shaker, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Man Against Himself, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Disillusioned Idealist, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Security on Networks, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Consult Commonwealth, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Botterdam Networks, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - New York + Environs & Legislative System, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - NSF Network, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Networks, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NSF Represent Network, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - A Policy Science and The Rhetoric of Controlled Comparison, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Introduction, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Theory and Method, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Recruitment and Structure, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - President In Staff, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - The Big Four, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Matthews Conference Seattle Outline+Texts, 1995 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Kentucky Confab State Legis. Elections, 1990 Mar (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Manifold, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Property Aggregation, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Preface, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Part-Whole + Reduction, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Mi-Na and The Part-Whole Problem, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Inequality and Heterogeneity, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Hechter Microfoundations, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Documents about Contextual Analysis, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NIE Proposal, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - He Notes, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Redwood Copy Use for Chapter 24, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Early 1970's Eulau-Jones-Zeigler, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Majority Rule and The Representative System of Governement, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Political Behavior General, 1955-1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Areas of Research (Socilization and Recruitment), 1961 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Some Modes of Analysis in the Social Sciences, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Eulau Graduate Students, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Various Journal Publications Secondary Resources, 1969-1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Various Journals, Notes, Publications, Secondary Resources, undated (Box 13, Folder 41641)
  - Redwood City Farr, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - American Academy of Arts & Sciences Call For Nominations, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Committees, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Behavior, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Guggenheim Book, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Polarity vs Dichotomy, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Mystery Stories, 1955-1962 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Letter of Correspondence about Book Review, 1991 Apr. 23 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - History + P.S., 1964-1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Encyclopedia of American Legislative Material, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Mass Pol, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - An Autopsy, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Primary Group, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Funbook Document, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Senate Ethics Hearings, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hoover Clippings, 1958 & 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - E35, undated (Box 14, Folder 41702)
  - Psychiatric Animals, 1975 Oct (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - The Manipulators: Personality and Politics in Multiple Perspectives, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Communication Research As A Behavioral Discipline, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Political Learning and Political Change Understanding Development Across Time, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EUI Working Paper No. 104, 1918-1967 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - The Significane of Class in American History and Politics, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Rationality of Unaminity and Non-Unamity (B40), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Long-Term Support for the National Election Studies, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Long-Term Support for the National Election Studies, 1998-2001 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Assorted Thoughts on The Study of Subgovernments (A57), undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Comparative Analysis, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bellagio Proposal + Rockfeller Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - How Comparative is Comparitve State Poltiics?, 1990 Mar (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Concepts of Class and Interest in Early American Consciousness, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Congress as research Arena--An Uneasy Partnership) A Review Essay, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Electoral Survey Data and the Temporal Dimension, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Masters' Model of Human Behavior as a Biological Phenomenon: The Issues of Levels and Reduction, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Electoral Survey Data and the Temporal Dimension, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Masters' Model of Human Behavior as a Biological Phenomenon: The Issue of Levels and Reduction, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 16 Of Urgency, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - P.S. 400B Casual Analysis, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Political Science: A New Synthesis, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - New Ch. 2 Of Tradition, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 5 Of Theory, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 4 Of Knowledge, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 2A of Pol. Sci. + Pol. Theory, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Bibliographies, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Articles, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Development Plan for ICPSR, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Study of Legislative Norms: An Intellectual History, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Study of Legislative Norms: An Intellectual History, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Norm Notes 1, 2, 3, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ch. 6 The Problem of Sanctions, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ch. 7 The Mystique of Influence, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ch. 5 The Problem of Conformity, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Ch. 1 The Gambits of Definitions, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Norms Introduction, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ency: Legislative Norms, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Ch.10 The Sawbols of Research, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Intellectual History Ch.3 The Legacy Part 3, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Intellectual History Ch.3 The Legacy Part 3, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Intellectual History Part II: The Matthews Legacy, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Ch.1 Political Encounters in Two Cultures - Ch. 9 Chasing the Interdisciplinary Bug, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Letter to Professor Watson, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Western European Conference on "Representation and the State", 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - File: reviewer.72, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Max Lerner's Mainstream American, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Etymology: The Journalist as Social Scientist, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - In the Beginning... Or: Whatever Happened to the Positivists Among Us?, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Soft Science, Hard Facts, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - In the Beginning... Or: Whatever Happened to the Positivists Among Us?, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Filename: spain.52, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - File: rebellio, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Filename: spain.52, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - File: oggray.1, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Filename: annual, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Filename: spain.52, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Contemporaneities, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - File: twelve.2, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Disk: obits.1, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - My View of Science, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Dimoque as Prologue, 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - APLS News, 1996 Dec. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - The Behavioral Movement at Fifty: Revolution, Revision, Return, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Introduction, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Exclusions: Rational and Irrational "Man", undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Ch. 5: Interdisciplinary Orientation, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - File: sorokin.1, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Letter to Aida Donald, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Preface, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Gunnell Paper, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - On Snowball Sampling, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Bellyache Democracy, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - "Name-Calling", undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Preface and Introduction, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Burke, 2002 May (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Chamberlain, 2002 Jul-Aug (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cowley, 2002 Apr (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Arvin, 2001 Nov (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Calverton, 2002 Apr (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Corey - Fraina, 2002 Mar (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dell, 2002 Jun (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Eastman, 2001 Nov (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Freeman, 2001 Nov (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, 2001 Aug (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hook, 2002 Feb (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Josephson, 2002 Feb (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - MacDonald, 2001 Aug (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - McCarthy, 2001 Nov (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Vorse, 2002 Jun (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - A, 2002 May (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - B, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - C, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - E, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - F, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - G, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - H, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - I-J, 2002 Apr (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - K, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - L, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - M, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - N, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - O, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - P, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Q-R, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - S, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - T, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - U-V, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - W, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - X-Y-Z, 2002 Apr (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Pre 1912, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - 1912-1917, Undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - 1917-1920, Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - 1920-1930, Undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - 1931-1939, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - 1940-1945, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 1961-1972, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - 1945-1960, 2002 Feb (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - 1973-, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Miscellany, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Outlines/Biblio, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - 1930s/General, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Communism/Party, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Overviews, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Journals/ Magazine, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Partisan Review, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - The Heyday of American Communism, undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - The Intellectuals Go Left, undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - The Heyday of American Communism, undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Infidel in the Temple: A memoir of the ninteen-thirties, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Czech Republic Slovakia, undated (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Heinz Eulau email correspondences, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - II. Chamberlain, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Selections from the Diary of Eleanor Anderson, 2003 Apr. 19 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - American Political Science Association, 2003 Apr. 29 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Email Addresses, 1999 Jan. 28 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Introduction to Socrates, 1998 Jan. 13 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Windows, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Introduction to Folio, 1998 Jan. 13 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Samson User Guide, 1994 Sep. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Information Technology Systems and Services, 1997 Aug. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - HE Mailing Lists, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - SUNet ID, etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - AufBau in Berlin, 2002 Feb. 7 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - HE References/ Biblio, 2002 Dec. 20 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Uri Aloni papers, 2003 Apr. 25 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Wills or Trusts?, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Marx in America: The New Deal, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Regent's Professor Warren E. Miller Receives Goodnow Award, 1999 Feb. 26 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Politics of Evron Kirkpatrick and the APSA, 2001 Oct. 31 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - The Forum: A Journal of Applied Research in Contemporary Politics, 2002 Jul 16 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Warran E. Miller and the Study of Comparative Politics: Mostly Some Personal Recollections and Reflections, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - J Stor Political Science papers, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - The War on Equality: State and Ideology in Contemporary America, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Gabriel A. Almond Memorial, 2003 Feb. 22 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Historical Political Science in the Behavioral Era, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Oral Presentation of Almond Tribute, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Gabriel Almond's Legacy: The Early Years, 2003 Aug. 29 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - APSA Member's Guide, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Alibris searches, 2003 Jun. 11 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - APSA Annual Meeting Preregistration, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - The New York Times: Op-Ed, 2003 Jun. 7 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - FOLDER: Newbook, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Lynne Rienner Publishers, 2003 Jun. 7 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - The More Time People Spend Using the Internet, 2000 Feb. 17 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - A Dialogue as Prologue: The Historian and the Behavioralist, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Antioch the Review, 1959-1960 Win. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Small Groups, Big Organizations, and Mass Society, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lobbyists: The Wasted Profession, 1964 Spr. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Political Behavior: A Reader in Theory and Research, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ch. 15 Social Science at the Crossroads, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Public Administration Review, 1962 Dec. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Occupational Mobility and Political Career, 1962 Sep. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American State Legislators' Role Orientations toward Pressure Groups, 22037 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The American Government: Democracy in Action, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Administration Review, 1959 Aut. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Latent Partisanship in Nonpartisan Elections: Effects of Political Milieu and Mobilization, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ch. 16 Political System and Political Behavior, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - H. D. Lasswell's Developmental Analysis, 1958 Jun. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Comparative Political Analysis: A Methodological Note, 1962 Nov. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Community Political Systems, Preface, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Social Science Quarterly, 1976 Jun. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Ideology and Discontent, Preface, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - City Councilmen and the Group Struggle: A Typology of Role Orientation, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Political Behavior in America: New Directions, Introduction, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Foreword, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Judicial Decision-Making, Preface, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - The Unwatered Hinterland of Political Science: Some Comments on the Occasion of a Premature Memorial Service, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Informal Organization of Decisional Structures in Small Legislative Bodies, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Party Systems and Voter Alignments: Cross-National Perspectives, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Decisional Structures and Coalition Formation in Small Legislative Bodies, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Career Perspectives of American State Legislators, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Ch. 19 The American Welfare State: Neither Ideology nor Utopia, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Bases of Authority in Legislative Bodies: A Comparative Analysis, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Identification with Class and Political Role Behavior, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - The Western Political Quarterly, 1955 Sep. (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Cleavage and Consensus in American Politics, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Identification with Class and Political Perspective, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Dimensions of Political Involvement, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - The Maddening Methods of Harold D. Lasswell: Some Philosophical Underpinnings, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - The Ecological Basis of Party Systems: The Case of Ohio, 1957 Aug. (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Book Review, 1966 Jan. (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - The Legislator as Specialist, 1960 Sep. (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - The Socialization of American State Legislators, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Perceptions of Class and Party in Voting Behavior: 1952, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Lippman Notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Assorted Eulau floppy disks, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Assorted cassettes, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - A Technical Report on Interpersonal Contexts of Political Behavior ("Network Analysis"), 1979 Jul. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Bibliography, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Electoral Process, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Columbia Studies of Personal Influence in Voting and Public Affairs, 1978 Jul.-Aug. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Contigent Rationality in Metropolitics: Research Note, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Legislative System and After: On Closing the Micro-Macro Gap, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Electoral Process, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Student Lawyer, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Collective Rationality in Legislative Policy-Making: A Research Note on Environmental Effects, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Conflict and Policy Integration in Legislative Committees, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Policy-making in American cities: comparisons in a quasi-longitudinal, quasi-experimental design, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Some Comments on Brian Barry's "Public Policy and Political Theory," and Some Findings from the Stanford City Council Research Project, 1971 Dec. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Social Bias in Leadership Selection, Political Recruitment, and Electoral Context, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Technology and the Fear of the Politics of Civility, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Decisional Structures in Small Legislative Bodies, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Toward the Suburban Reshaping of American Politics, 1975 Win. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - The Puzzle of Representation: Specifying Components of Responsiveness, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Skill Revolution and Consultative Commonwealth, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Political Matrix and Political Repreentation: Prolegomenon to a New Departure from an Old Problem, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Changing Patterns of Military Politics, Preface, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Ch. 2 Units and Levels of Analysis, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - City Councils and Policy Outcomes: Developmental Profiles, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Policy Maps of City Councils and Policy Outcomes: A Developmental Analysis, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Political Socialization and Political Roles, 1966-1967 Win. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Legislative Institutions and Processes, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - High Priests of Politics, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Comment on Professor Deutsch's Paper, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Some Potential Effects of the Information Utility on Political Decision-Makers and the Role of the Representative, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Policy-making in American cities: comparisons in a quasi-longitudinal, quasi-experimental design, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Recent Research on Congress in a Democratic Perspective, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Toward the Federal Polity, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Political Norms Affecting Decisions Concerning Higher Education, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 33)